https://americancomposers.org//privacy-policy

ACO Privacy Policy
American Composers Orchestra (ACO) adopted this privacy policy to inform users of the americancomposers.org and orchestratech.org websites how the sites collect, store, and use personal information submitted via the site(s).
1. Collection of information
Certain features on the website may require users to provide personal information in order to make a commerce transaction or to receive concert announcements via electronic delivery. Such personal information is not shared or sold to third parties. To better understand the needs of our website users, we may also request demographic information. Entry of such information is optional. If we request demographic information, we will not share information about you as an individual with any other entity. If we do share demographic information with third parties, we will give them aggregate information only.
2. Mailing lists
If you provide your e-mail address, ACO may periodically contact you with special offers, updated information, and new services. Any e-mails sent to you by ACO offer you the option to be removed from the e-mail mailing list.
Our website allows visitors to subscribe to our mailing list by providing their names and addresses. If you provide us with your mailing address or telephone number, ACO, in addition to providing you with concert announcements, may also use this information to alert you to updated information and new services. If you wish to be removed from the mailing list, you may do so by contacting ACO directly. (See the “Contact us” section below).
3. Contact us/How to update your personal information
You may help ACO maintain the accuracy of your personal information by notifying us when you change your address, title, phone number, or e-mail address. Contact us via email at aco@americancomposers.org or at (212) 977-8495 if you wish to update your information or if you no longer wish to receive communications. Further contact information is listed on the americancomposers.org homepage.
Please include both your old and new contact information so that we can make the appropriate corrections. ACO would like to receive your comments or questions about this privacy policy. Please address comments or questions regarding ACO’s privacy practices to us at the email address listed above. ACO may occasionally update this policy. Notice of revisions will be posted here.
212-977-8495
info@americancomposers.org
494 8th Ave, Suite 503, New York, NY 10001
Our Mission & Vision
American Composers Orchestra (ACO) is dedicated to the creation, celebration, performance, and promotion of orchestral music by American composers. With commitment to diversity, disruption and discovery, ACO produces concerts, pre-college and college education programs, and emerging composer professional development to foster a community of creators, audience, performers, collaborators, and funders.
ACO
About ACO
Contact
Join ACO Community
Newsroom
Listen, Watch, Explore
Educational Programs
Performances & Events
Join Our Mailing List!
Get notified about new events, opportunities and the latest ACO happenings
